Guide to the Administrative Files of the Dean of the School of Education, Daniel E. Griffiths 1948-1985 (Bulk 1965-1983) RG 26.0.1 RG.26.0.1
New York University Archives
- Griffiths Container List
  - Department of Organization and Administrative Studies, 1976-1978 (Box 35, Folder 15)
  - Report on Management on Declining Enrollments, undated (Box 35, Folder 16)
  - Admission, Undergraduate Statistics, 1979-1980 (Box 36, Folder 1)
    bar code#: 3 1142 04058 206 9
  - Anderson Fellows, 1977-1978 (Box 36, Folder 2)
  - A Functional Analysis of the 1977-1978 New York City Board of Education, undated (Box 36, Folder 3)
  - Board of Examiners Project, 1978 (Box 36, Folder 4)
  - Budget Advisory Committee, 1978-1979 (Box 36, Folder 5)
  - Center for Career Advancement, 1976-1978 (Box 36, Folder 6)
  - Deans Development Fund Research Proposals, 1978-1979 (Box 36, Folder 7)
  - Deans, Division Heads, Department Chairpersons Meetings, 1977-1979 (Box 36, Folder 8)
  - Development Trips, 1978-1979 (Box 37, Folder 1)
    bar code#: 3 1142 04058 207 7
  - Division Heads, 1978 (Box 37, Folder 2)
  - Education Associates, 1972-1977 (Box 37, Folder 3)
  - Evaluation of Department Chairpeople, 1975-1978 (Box 37, Folder 4)
  - Evaluation of Division Heads, 1973 (Box 37, Folder 5)
  - Faculty Staffing Strategies, 1977-1978 (Box 38, Folder 1)
    bar code#: 3 1142 04058 208 5
  - Financial Aid and Financial Aid Survey, 1971-1978 (Box 38, Folder 2)
  - Para-Educator Center, 1975-1979 (Box 38, Folder 3)
  - Para-Educator Center Board of Directors, 1978-1979 (Box 38, Folder 4)
  - Para-Educator Commencements, 1976-1976 (Box 38, Folder 5)
  - Petty Cash Vouchers, 1973-1980 (Box 38, Folder 6)
  - Phi Delta Kappa, 1974-1979 (Box 38, Folder 7)
  - Pinkerton Foundation, undated (Box 38, Folder 8)
  - Placement, 1968-1979 (Box 38, Folder 9)
  - Placement - Job Opportunity Bulletins, 1979-1981 (Box 38, Folder 10)
  - Puerto Rico Commencements, 1971-1978 (Box 38, Folder 11)
  - Puerto Rico Correspondence, 1973-1979 (Box 38, Folder 12)
  - Reporgraphic Services, 1976-1979 (Box 38, Folder 13)
  - Request for Check, 1974-1979 (Box 38, Folder 14)
  - Salary Study, 1977-1978 (Box 38, Folder 15)
  - Salary Study, 1978-1979 (Box 38, Folder 16)
  - Student Registration, 1971-1978 (Box 38, Folder 17)
  - Student Teaching, 1968-1978 (Box 39, Folder 1)
    bar code#: 3 1142 04058 209 3
  - UCEA Review, 1974-1979 (Box 39, Folder 2)
  - UCEA Review, Letter to Editor, 1976 (Box 39, Folder 3)
  - Travel Expense Voucher, 1973-1978 (Box 39, Folder 4)
  - Administration Management Council, 1974-1977 (Box 39, Folder 5)
  - Admissions, Undergraduate Office of, 1973-1976 (Box 39, Folder 6)
  - Affirmative Action, 1973-1976 (Box 39, Folder 7)
  - Afro-American Affairs, Institute of, 1970-1976 (Box 39, Folder 8)
  - Alumni Association Board of Directors, SEHNAP, 1975-1978 (Box 39, Folder 9)
  - Alumni Fund Reports, 1970-1978 (Box 39, Folder 10)
  - Alumni Giving Status Reports, 1970-1977 (Box 39, Folder 11)
  - Arts and Science, Faculty of (FAS), 1969-1978 (Box 39, Folder 12)
  - Arts and Science, Graduate School of, 1972-1977 (Box 39, Folder 13)
  - Arts and Science, Washington Square and University College, 1972-1979 (Box 39, Folder 14)
  - Arts, School of, 1968-1978 (Box 39, Folder 15)
  - Benefits, 1973-1978 (Box 39, Folder 16)
  - Business Administration, Graduate School of, 1968-1975 (Box 39, Folder 17)
  - Business and Public Administration, School of, 1970-1976 (Box 39, Folder 18)
  - C.W. Post - NYU Doctoral Programs Task Force, 1976-1978 (Box 39, Folder 19)
  - Challenge Fund Proposals, 1976-1979 (Box 39, Folder 20)
  - Challenge Grants, 1979 (Box 39, Folder 21)
  - Research Challenge Fund, 1979 (Box 39, Folder 22)
  - Coffee - Central Convenience Items, 1974-1978 (Box 39, Folder 23)
  - Continuing Education, School of, 1971-1978 (Box 39, Folder 24)
  - DRAT (Deafness Research and Training Center), 1976-1977 (Box 40, Folder 1)
    bar code#: 3 1142 04058 210 1
  - DRAT Correspondence, 1978-1979 (Box 40, Folder 2)
  - DRAT National Advisory Board, 1974-1978 (Box 40, Folder 3)
  - DRAT RSA Site Visit, 1977 (Box 40, Folder 4)
  - DRAT Progress Report # 12, 1977-1978 (Box 40, Folder 5)
  - DRAT (National Interpreter Training Consortium), undated (Box 40, Folder 6)
  - DRAT (Television Proposals WNBC-WNET), undated (Box 40, Folder 7)
  - Demonstration Program, undated (Box 40, Folder 8)
  - Deans Council, 1971-1973 (Box 40, Folder 9)
  - Deans Council, 1977-1978 (Box 40, Folder 10)
  - Deans Development Fund, 1974-1978 (Box 40, Folder 11)
  - Deans List - Students, 1975-1978 (Box 40, Folder 12)
  - Dentistry, College of, 1976-1978 (Box 40, Folder 13)
  - Development Programs, SENAP's Office of, 1972-1977 (Box 40, Folder 14)
  - Dissertation Research Fee, Research of, 1972-1973 (Box 41, Folder 1)
    bar code#: 3 1142 04058 211 9
  - Division Heads Meeting, 1970-1977 (Box 41, Folder 2)
  - Division Heads Correspondence, 1971-1977 (Box 41, Folder 3)
  - Educational Administration Quarterly, 1975-1978 (Box 41, Folder 4)
  - Education Quarterly, NYU, 1973-1979 (Box 41, Folder 5)
  - Faculty Evaluation Procedures, Ad Hoc Committee, undated (Box 41, Folder 6)
  - Faculty Evaluations, 1977 (Box 41, Folder 7)
  - Faculty Loads, Committee to Study, 1977-1978 (Box 41, Folder 8)
  - Faculty Listings, 1973-1974 (Box 41, Folder 9)
  - Faculty Listings, 1977-1978 (Box 41, Folder 10)
  - Faculty Meetings, 1977-1979 (Box 41, Folder 11)
  - Faculty Service on Dissertation Committee, 1978 (Box 41, Folder 12)
  - Faculty Unemployment Insurance Claims - A Summary Report, 1975 (Box 41, Folder 13)
  - Farr Committee on Graduate and Professional Education at NYU, 1974 (Box 41, Folder 14)
  - Founders Day, 1971-1978 (Box 41, Folder 15)
  - Foundation Appeal, NY, 1972 (Box 41, Folder 16)
  - Gifts, 1975-1979 (Box 41, Folder 17)
  - Graduate Commission, 1977-1978 (Box 41, Folder 18)
  - HEOP (Higher Education Opportunities Program), 1968-1978 (Box 41, Folder 19)
  - ISP (Informative Systems Plan), 1976 (Box 41, Folder 20)
  - IDS (Institute of Developmental Studies), 1969-1977 (Box 41, Folder 21)
  - IDS (Institute of Developmental Studies), 1976-1978 (Box 42, Folder 1)
    bar code#: 3 1142 04058 212 7
  - IDS Model Cities - Early Childhood Resource Centers, 1976-1977 (Box 42, Folder 2)
  - Land Grant - General, 1977-1978 (Box 42, Folder 3)
  - Language Requirement for Ph.D. - Guerra, undated (Box 42, Folder 4)
  - Library Committee, 1970-1973 (Box 42, Folder 5)
  - Mailings to Faculty, 1972-1977 (Box 42, Folder 6)
  - Metro Center, 1978 (Box 42, Folder 7)
  - Financial Reports, 1974-1978 (Box 42, Folder 8)
  - Financial Reports, 1970-1974 (Box 43, Folder 1)
    bar code#: 3 1142 04058 213 5
  - Calendars, 1973-1979 (Box 43, Folder 2)
  - AERA Symposium, 1975 (Box 44, Folder 1)
    bar code#: 3 1142 04058 214 3
  - Budget Meeting with President Sawhill et al, 1975 (Box 44, Folder 2)
  - SEHNAP Budget Faculty Salaries, 1975-1976 (Box 44, Folder 3)
  - NYU - Projected Cost Accounting, 1974-1975 (Box 44, Folder 4)
  - Budget, 1975-1976 (Box 44, Folder 5)
  - NYU - Budget Guidelines and Procedures for 1976-77 Budgets, 1976-1977 (Box 44, Folder 6)
  - SEHNAP - Projected Expenses, 1976-1977 (Box 44, Folder 7)
  - Challenge Fund, 1977 (Box 44, Folder 8)
  - Childress Report - Two Day visit to NYU School of Education, 1970 (Box 44, Folder 9)
  - Collective Bargaining, undated (Box 44, Folder 10)
  - Creative Leadership Award, 1968-1978 (Box 44, Folder 11)
  - NYU Deans Council, 1975-1976 (Box 44, Folder 12)
  - Decentralization, undated (Box 44, Folder 13)
  - Divisional Meeting, 1974-1975 (Box 45, Folder 1)
    bar code#: 3 1142 04058 215 0
  - Education Building - Proposed Plans for, undated (Box 45, Folder 2)
  - Education Quarterly Editorial Board, 1971-1978 (Box 45, Folder 3)
  - Evaluation of the Dean, 1978 (Box 45, Folder 4)
  - Report on Planning for the Future of the NYU School of Education, 1975 (Box 45, Folder 5)
  - Goals Statement, 1975 (Box 45, Folder 6)
  - Graduate Commission, 1974-1976 (Box 45, Folder 7)
  - Implications of Organizational Structure for Planning - Clearwater, FL, 1976 (Box 45, Folder 8)
  - NYU - Institute for Retail Management, undated (Box 45, Folder 9)
  - ICET - International Council on Education for Teaching, undated (Box 45, Folder 10)
  - IMTEC - Bicentennial Training Programme, undated (Box 45, Folder 11)
  - Kowalski, Tony, undated (Box 45, Folder 12)
  - Library Committee - Subcommittee of SEHNAP Council, undated (Box 45, Folder 13)
  - NYU - LUCHA, undated (Box 45, Folder 14)
  - NYU - Martin Luther King Scholars, undated (Box 45, Folder 15)
  - Mayher, John - Division Head, Department of Education, 1973-1976 (Box 45, Folder 16)
  - NYU Middle States Association Program on Graduate and Professional Ed., undated (Box 45, Folder 17)
  - Ontario Council for Leadership in Educational Administration, 1974 (Box 45, Folder 18)
  - Ontario Institute for Studies in Education, Toronto, 1974 (Box 45, Folder 19)
  - Para - Educator Center, 1971-1975 (Box 45, Folder 20)
  - Para - Educator Center Board of Directors, 1975-1977 (Box 46, Folder 1)
    bar code#: 3 1142 04058 216 8
  - Sch Ed Personnel Information, undated (Box 46, Folder 2)
  - Public Occasions, Bureau of Arthur Rubin, undated (Box 46, Folder 3)
  - Publications Systems, Undergraduate Committee to Study, 1977 (Box 46, Folder 4)
  - SEHNAP Report of the Committee on Student Recruitment, undated (Box 46, Folder 5)
  - Sch Ed Research Colloqium, 1971 (Box 46, Folder 6)
  - Roosevelt Island Schools, undated (Box 46, Folder 7)
  - Faculty Salary Study, 1976-1977 (Box 46, Folder 8)
  - Faculty Salary Study Analysis, National, 1973-1977 (Box 46, Folder 9)
  - Sch Ed Speech Rehabilitation Institute, undated (Box 46, Folder 10)
  - Spencer Foundation Seed Grants, 1977-1980 (Box 46, Folder 11)
  - Student Projections for 1975 (O'Mara's), undated (Box 46, Folder 12)
  - Town Hall, undated (Box 46, Folder 13)
  - Undergraduate Education, Committee on, 1975-1976 (Box 46, Folder 14)
  - Undergraduate Education Questionnaire - Marilyn Moffat, undated (Box 46, Folder 15)
  - UCEA Seminar, 1976 (Box 46, Folder 16)
  - Warburg, Edward, undated (Box 46, Folder 17)
  - Washington Square Council, undated (Box 46, Folder 18)
  - Weckstein Lecture, 1970-1977 (Box 47, Folder 1)
    bar code#: 3 1142 04058 217 6
  - Dilemma of the Deanship, 1974-1976 (Box 47, Folder 2)
  - Annual Reports, 1975-1976 (Box 48, Folder 1)
    bar code#: 3 1142 04058 218 4
  - SEHNAP Problems and Objectives, 1976-1977 (Box 48, Folder 2)
  - Motion #55, 1974 (Box 48, Folder 3)
  - Address to NYU School of Ed Faculty, 1973 (Box 48, Folder 4)
  - Dean's Report, 1974 (Box 48, Folder 5)
  - Address to Education Faculty, 1974 (Box 48, Folder 6)
  - Annual Report, 1966-1967 (Box 48, Folder 7)
  - Department Program Files, 1976-1980 (Box 49, Folder 1)
    bar code#: 3 1142 04058 219 2
  - Health Education, 1974-1979 (Box 50, Folder 1)
    bar code#: 3 1142 04058 220 0
  - Occupational Health and Safety, 1974-1980 (Box 50, Folder 2)
  - Occupational Therapy, 1976-1980 (Box 50, Folder 3)
  - Physical Therapy, 1974-1980 (Box 50, Folder 4)
  - Prosthetics and Orthotics, 1975-1979 (Box 50, Folder 5)
  - Division of Nursing, 1975-1980 (Box 50, Folder 6)
  - Rehabilitation Counseling, 1973-1980 (Box 50, Folder 7)
  - Research and Theory Development in Nursing Science, 1978 (Box 50, Folder 8)
  - Nursing Department Chairs to be Filled, 1977 (Box 50, Folder 9)
  - Advanced Education in Nursing Science, 1977-1980 (Box 50, Folder 10)
  - Division of Arts and Arts Education, 1974-1980 (Box 50, Folder 11)
  - Art and Art Education, 1973-1980 (Box 50, Folder 12)
  - Dance and Dance Education, 1974-1979 (Box 50, Folder 13)
  - Music and Music Education, 1973-1980 (Box 50, Folder 14)
  - Technology and Industrial Education, 1974-1979 (Box 50, Folder 15)
  - Budget Advisory Committee, 1977-1978 (Box 50, Folder 16)
  - Budget Advisory Committee, 1976-1977 (Box 50, Folder 17)
  - Budget Advisory Committee, 1975-1976 (Box 50, Folder 18)
  - Budget Advisory Committee, 1974-1975 (Box 50, Folder 19)
  - Samuel T. Burneson, 1970-1977 (Box 50, Folder 20)
  - Faculty Loads: Nursing, 1975-1976 (Box 50, Folder 21)
  - Faculty Loads: Arts, 1975-1976 (Box 50, Folder 22)
  - Faculty Loads Studies, 1974-1976 (Box 50, Folder 23)
  - Faculty Loads: Education, 1975-1976 (Box 50, Folder 24)
  - Faculty Loads - Health, 1975-1976 (Box 51, Folder 1)
    bar code#: 3 1142 04058 221 8
  - Faculty Meetings, 1972-1977 (Box 51, Folder 2)
  - Faculty Meeting Minutes, 1975-1978 (Box 51, Folder 3)
  - Governance Committee of the Faculty Council, 1969-1972 (Box 51, Folder 4)
  - Faculty Council, Commmitee on Committees of the, 1969-1972 (Box 51, Folder 5)
  - Admissions Committee of the Faculty Council, 1970-1971 (Box 51, Folder 6)
  - Issues Committee of the Faculty Council, 1970-1972 (Box 51, Folder 7)
  - Research Committee Report to the Faculty Council, undated (Box 51, Folder 8)
  - Educational Council, 1972-1975 (Box 51, Folder 9)
  - Faculty Council (now called Educational Council), 1971-1972 (Box 51, Folder 10)
  - Evaluation of Department Chairpeople, 1977-1978 (Box 52, Folder 1)
    bar code#: 3 1142 04058 222 6
  - Deans Group Minutes, 1974-1976 (Box 52, Folder 2)
  - Deans Weekly Meetings with the Chancellor, 1974-1976 (Box 52, Folder 3)
  - Deans Weekly Meetings with the President, 1974-1976 (Box 53, Folder 1)
    bar code#: 3 1142 04058 223 4
  - NYU Deans Council Meetings, 1971-1975 (Box 53, Folder 2)
  - NYU Senate Meetings, 1975-1977 (Box 53, Folder 3)
  - NYU Senate Meetings, 1974-1975 (Box 54, Folder 1)
    bar code#: 3 1142 04058 224 2
  - NYU Senate Rules Committee, 1975 (Box 54, Folder 2)
  - Goals Study, 1973 (Box 54, Folder 3)
  - William Payne, Executive Vice President, undated (Box 54, Folder 4)
  - William F. Payne, Deans Review of Vice Presidential Areas, undated (Box 54, Folder 5)
  - Peter Ames - Correspondence, undated (Box 54, Folder 6)
  - Bachelor's Degree Graduates, 1971-1973 (Box 54, Folder 7)
  - Environmental Health Sciences, Proposal for Interdepartmental Program, 1974 (Box 54, Folder 8)
  - Fee Changes, 1976-1977 (Box 54, Folder 9)
  - Faculty - Dutch Treat Luncheons, 1975 (Box 54, Folder 10)
  - Faculty Salaries - Equalization of Male and Female Salaries, 1973 (Box 54, Folder 11)
  - Investiture of President Sawhill, 1975 (Box 54, Folder 12)
  - Minutes - President's Meeting, 1976-1977 (Box 54, Folder 13)
  - Samuel T. Burmeson - Asst. Chancellor for Admin. And Space, 1970-1977 (Box 54, Folder 14)
  - Training for the Education of all Children with Handicaps in the US, undated (Box 54, Folder 15)
  - Clearinghouse for Bilingual Education, A Proposal for, 1977 (Box 54, Folder 16)
  - AACTE (General Board of Directors), undated (Box 54, Folder 17)
  - Land Grant, 1973-1976 (Box 55, Folder 1)
    bar code#: 3 1142 04058 225 9
  - Albany - New York Higher Education Assistance Corp., undated (Box 55, Folder 2)
  - Planning Conference on Teacher Effectiveness, Saratoga Springs, 1973 (Box 55, Folder 3)
  - Ohio State - Conference on Educational Administration, undated (Box 55, Folder 4)
  - Society on Research Administrators, undated (Box 55, Folder 5)
  - Research Training Panel - Egermeier, Washington D.C., undated (Box 55, Folder 6)
  - National Institute of Education, undated (Box 55, Folder 7)
  - AASA - Bulletins, etc., undated (Box 55, Folder 8)
  - Examiner, Board of Education, Civil Service Commission Exam, 1974 (Box 55, Folder 9)
  - United Federation of Teachers, 1969-1974 (Box 55, Folder 10)
  - Cleveland Conference, 1963-1973 (Box 55, Folder 11)
  - HEW - Bureau of Education for the Handicapped, undated (Box 55, Folder 12)
  - Unit 2: In the Preparation and Practice of Prof. For Elem and Sec. Ed., undated (Box 55, Folder 13)
  - Research for Better Schools, undated (Box 55, Folder 14)
  - AACTE - MINFO, undated (Box 55, Folder 15)
  - Cases: IRC-UMW Cases and Others, undated (Box 56, Folder 1)
    bar code#: 3 1142 04058 226 7
  - Register of Educational Research, undated (Box 56, Folder 2)
  - Civic Assembly, 1968 (Box 56, Folder 3)
  - Civil Service Appt, undated (Box 56, Folder 4)
  - Courses of Study in School Administration, undated (Box 56, Folder 5)
  - Croft Educational Services: Correspondence, undated (Box 56, Folder 6)
  - Critical Difference Computer, undated (Box 56, Folder 7)
  - Daniel R. Davies, undated (Box 56, Folder 8)
  - Dean Conference - Blackstone, Chicago, 1968 (Box 56, Folder 9)
  - Expenses, undated (Box 56, Folder 10)
  - NCAHE, 1970 (Box 56, Folder 11)
  - NEA, undated (Box 56, Folder 12)
  - New York Academy of Public Education, undated (Box 56, Folder 13)
  - NEA Commission of Professional Rights and Responsibilities, undated (Box 56, Folder 14)
  - 22nd National Conference of Professors of Educational Administration, 1968 (Box 56, Folder 15)
  - National Registration Office, undated (Box 56, Folder 16)
  - New Hyde Park, NY, 1966 (Box 56, Folder 17)
  - NSSE Correspondence, undated (Box 56, Folder 18)
  - NSSE Discussions in Atlantic City, 1963 (Box 56, Folder 19)
  - NSSE Permissions to quote, undated (Box 56, Folder 20)
  - US Office of Education Meeting, 1968 (Box 56, Folder 21)
  - One Experimental Laboratory, undated (Box 56, Folder 22)
  - Permission to reprint, undated (Box 56, Folder 23)
  - PEA Board of Trustees, 1968 (Box 56, Folder 24)
  - PEA Board of Trustees, undated (Box 56, Folder 25)
  - PEA Committee on School Adminstration and Legislation, undated (Box 56, Folder 26)
  - PEA General, 1962-1969 (Box 57, Folder 1)
    bar code#: 3 1142 04058 227 5
  - Personal Finances, 1963 (Box 57, Folder 2)
  - Philosophy Circle, 1962-1964 (Box 57, Folder 3)
  - Placement (also Personal Correspondence), 1962-1964 (Box 57, Folder 4)
  - Planning Board for the Examination for Examiner, 1965-1966 (Box 57, Folder 5)
  - Plans for Summer of 1965, 1962-1965 (Box 57, Folder 6)
  - Proposed Policy on Drugs at NYU, undated (Box 57, Folder 7)
  - Letters of Recommendation, 1965 (Box 57, Folder 8)
  - Regents Advisory Board on Teacher Education, Certification, and Practice, 1965 (Box 57, Folder 9)
  - Register of Educational Research (Croft), 1966-1968 (Box 57, Folder 10)
  - Research Ideas, 1964 (Box 57, Folder 11)
  - Special Commission to Study the Entire Field of Education, 1965 (Box 57, Folder 12)
  - Rivlin: Proposal, 1965 (Box 57, Folder 13)
  - Roslyn, L.I.: Board of Education Meeting of Board, 1963 (Box 57, Folder 14)
  - TCC Re-Union, 1960 (Box 57, Folder 15)
  - Sabbatical - Universal Aunts Ltd., 1968-1969 (Box 57, Folder 16)
  - Sabbatical Leave - to be kept in Office, 1966-1970 (Box 57, Folder 17)
  - School Board Relationship - Campbell, 1961 (Box 57, Folder 18)
  - School-Community Committee for Educational Excellence, 1965 (Box 57, Folder 19)
  - Science Curriculum Improvement Study, 1965 (Box 57, Folder 20)
  - Selection Board Member for Coordinator for Rescheduling the School Year, 1968 (Box 57, Folder 21)
  - Seminar on TOBE Project for Ontario Institute for Studies in Education, 1969 (Box 57, Folder 22)
  - Separation of Church and School, undated (Box 57, Folder 23)
  - Social Science Research Council: Items, 1966, 1968 (Box 57, Folder 24)
  - Society for General Systems Research, 1962 (Box 57, Folder 25)
  - Speakers: Suggestions, 1963 (Box 57, Folder 26)
  - Superintendents Certificates (NYS), undated (Box 57, Folder 27)
  - System Development Corp., 1962-1963 (Box 57, Folder 28)
  - CDPSA Staffing Booklets, undated (Box 57, Folder 29)
  - Income Tax, 1967-1968 (Box 57, Folder 30)
  - For Tax Purposes, 1968 (Box 57, Folder 31)
  - Tax, 1963-1967 (Box 57, Folder 32)
  - Teachers College Doctoral Program, undated (Box 57, Folder 33)
  - "Technology and Educational Administration" Conference, 1968 (Box 57, Folder 34)
  - TIAA CREF, 1962, 1964 (Box 57, Folder 35)
  - Trends in the Study of School Adminstration, 1964 (Box 57, Folder 36)
  - Trustees' Meeting, 1966 (Box 57, Folder 37)
  - Union - Endicott, School Board Management Project, 1964 (Box 57, Folder 38)
  - US Steel Foundation, Inc., 1962 (Box 57, Folder 39)
  - University Seminar #423, undated (Box 58, Folder 1)
    bar code#: 3 1142 04058 228 3
  - USOE Educational Processes Panel, 1965 (Box 58, Folder 2)
  - USOE Educational Processes Panel Meeting in NYC, 1965 (Box 58, Folder 3)
  - USOE Educational Processes Panel Meeting, 1967 (Box 58, Folder 4)
  - Villonova's Work-Study Conference, 1968 (Box 58, Folder 5)
  - Who's Who in the East, 1966 (Box 58, Folder 6)
  - Who's Who and other directories, 1966 (Box 58, Folder 7)
  - Thank you's for services, undated (Box 58, Folder 8)
  - Campaign Progress Reports, 1970-1975 (Box 59, Folder 1)
    bar code#: 3 1142 04058 229 1
  - Capital Campaign Correspondence, 1967-1973 (Box 59, Folder 2)
  - SEHNAP Capital News, undated (Box 59, Folder 3)
  - Danforth Foundation, 1963-1969 (Box 59, Folder 4)
  - Endeavor Foundation, 1968 (Box 59, Folder 5)
  - Esso Foundation, 1972 (Box 59, Folder 6)
  - Ford Foundation - FCC, 1966 (Box 59, Folder 7)
  - Ford - Rockefeller Research Awards, 1975 (Box 59, Folder 8)
  - Nathan A. Karr - Capital Campaign, undated (Box 59, Folder 9)
  - Henry Kaufmann Foundation, 1967 (Box 59, Folder 10)
  - Kettering Foundation, 1967 (Box 59, Folder 11)
  - Kresge Foundation, 1967 (Box 59, Folder 12)
  - Livingston Institute, 1964-1965 (Box 59, Folder 13)
  - New York Foundation (Proposal for Ed Drama Center), 1975 (Box 59, Folder 14)
  - Proctor and Gamble, 1973 (Box 59, Folder 15)
  - Scholarships, Interns, etc. Misc., undated (Box 59, Folder 16)
  - Alfred P. Sloan Foundatio, undated (Box 59, Folder 17)
  - Stern Family Fund, 1968 (Box 59, Folder 18)
  - Westinghouse, 1965 (Box 59, Folder 19)
  - Alumni General, 1962-1975 (Box 60, Folder 1)
    bar code#: 3 1142 04058 230 9
  - Dean Walter Anderson Memorial Dedication, undated (Box 60, Folder 2)
  - Anderson Fellows Membership Lists, undated (Box 60, Folder 3)
  - Anderson Room Fund Campaign Letters, undated (Box 60, Folder 4)
  - Anderson Fellows, 1964-1976 (Box 60, Folder 5)
  - Anderson Seminar - Materials Used for Discussions, undated (Box 60, Folder 6)
  - Anderson Seminar, 1974-1975 (Box 60, Folder 7)
  - Westchester County Education Alumni, undated (Box 60, Folder 8)
  - Dean's Evaluation of Department Chairpeople, 1975 (Box 60, Folder 9)
  - New York City Temporary Commission on Education - Correspondence, 1977 (Box 61, Folder 1)
    bar code#: 3 1142 04058 231 7
  - New York City Temporary Commission on Education - Public Hearing, 1977 (Box 61, Folder 2)
  - Comm. Task Force on Teacher Education / Certification - Drafts, 1977 (Box 61, Folder 3)
  - Comm. Task Force on Teacher Education / Certification - Correspondence, 1975-1978 (Box 61, Folder 4)
  - Comm. Task Force on Teacher Education / Certification - Meetings, 1975-1976 (Box 61, Folder 5)
  - Comm. Task Force on Teacher Education / Certification - Meetings, 1976-1976 (Box 61, Folder 6)
  - New York City Temporary Commission on Education - Report to Mayor, 1977 (Box 61, Folder 7)
  - UCEA COrrespondence, 1970-1976 (Box 61, Folder 8)
  - UCEA Newsletters, 1970-1972 (Box 61, Folder 9)
  - UCEA Instructional Resources Catalog, 1973-1976 (Box 61, Folder 10)
  - UCEA Partnership, 1974-1975 (Box 61, Folder 11)
  - Teacher Education Conference Board, 1973-1978 (Box 62, Folder 1)
    bar code#: 3 1142 04058 232 5
  - State Education Department, 1970-1974 (Box 62, Folder 2)
  - Teacher Certification, 1972 (Box 62, Folder 3)
  - State Education Department, 1964-1965 (Box 62, Folder 4)
  - Recertification of Programs for Speech and Hearing Handicapped, 1975 (Box 62, Folder 5)
  - US Office of Education and other Government Agencies, 1969-1971 (Box 62, Folder 6)
  - New York State Deans Council, 1972-1975 (Box 62, Folder 7)
  - Dated Files, 1973-1979 (Box 63, Folder 1)
    bar code#: 3 1142 04058 194 7